TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Ukeme Essien.
I was trained
on oil and gas production operations.
Since I completed the training in December 2007,
I had not have a job for six years.
I have been everywhere, went to so many companies,
did the interviews and medical check-ups,
but there was always an excuse
why I wasn't given the job.
I came to The SCOAN in April this year.
When I came, I got the Anointing
Water and anointed myself.
That was on Sunday, 7th of April.
I had this overseas connection that refused to answer my calls.
It was a recruitment organisation.
Immediately after I anointed myself on that Sunday,
on Monday morning at 7:24 am, on the 8th of April,
I received a call from overseas.
They told me they wanted to see me in the United Arab Emirates
for a face to face interview.
So, they paid my ticket, paid for accommodation in a 5
star hotel in UAE, Abu Dhabi.
Only 35 people were invited for
the interview from all over the world.
Only two people were from Africa among those 35 -
me and one other man from Lagos, Nigeria.
When they called me for the interview,
I excused myself to go to the toilet and they approved.
When I got to the toilet, I used the Anointing Water and....
Mr. Ukeme Essien
Anointing Water Testimony
I sprayed the Anointing Water all over myself
until I almost emptied the bottle.
I said that as soon as they would see my
face, they should see favour,
that I didn't want them to ask me
any question I didn't know.
And that if there would be any question I would not know - if they would ask me, they should answer it.
So I got in there, and one of the white men that was interviewing us -
because I was the least among the 35, the youngest one -
he looked at me again and again
and I could read his mind.
It was like: "What is this small baby doing here among these adults?"
So, they called me in. As soon as I opened the door and went in,
the white men there started laughing.
It was, as if they have known me before.
I was scared - could
they be drunk or something?
Any little thing I said, they laughed
and they would be so happy.
They interviewed me for one hour
and for every answer I gave they told me to go deeper and explain more.
After everything, they asked me the only question which I did not know.
I spent like 10 seconds trying to
think about it and they answered it for me.
So I knew that the Anointing Water was at work.
They took me for medical check-ups
and when I got there, there was an announcement
that if you were more than 45 years old, you should come for another check-up.
So when I saw the people that were sitting with me stand up,
I joined them to stand up.
So when I got there, the American doctor that was doing the check-up
said, "Go, sit down, you are a child,
I am talking about adults, you are a child, go, sit down."
So everybody started laughing at me.
So at the end, they gave me this appointment letter.
Praise the Lord!
I am entitled to a brand new car every two years
and the payment is over 14 million naira.
That is my payment, that is what
they will pay me.
And a very big house going for
4.7 million naira every year rent.
I decided not to hide such a testimony.
I said I should come and share it for the glory of God.
They made me the field services foreman,
which is the head of all the technicians.
So I thank God.
Praise God.
Which company?
The name of the company is
Abu Dhabi Company for Onshore Oil Operations.
It's an oil company, this is their clinic where they did my medical check-ups.
This is the five star hotel where they lodge me.
What were you doing before,
from the level you were before to this new level?
Tell us.
Before, I was just moving around teaching in secondary schools.
On the streets?
Yes, and they were paying me 8000 Naira per month.
No, look! Don't say this in public.
Part time teaching - in the evening he
would go to school and teach the children.
From morning to evening he would
be moving in the streets roaming about.
8000 to millions.
Mr Ukeme Essien
Anointing Water Testimony
This is what I heard from God when
I was given this Anointing Water.
The transformation will be so great.
Anointing Water Testimony
Look, brother, to go on and on, your first salary -
you should only take the money you need for transport and food.
Take it and look round for the less privileged and raise their standard.
Anointing Water Testimony
After that, you can begin to
remove money
that will not affect you, your living.
Remove it and put it down and continue to take care of the less privileged.
If you do that, in six month you will be transferred
from this place to another place.
Praise the Lord!
Be a good citizen as you are going.
Please, be a good citizen.
The name of your country, please - it is very dear.
Thank you, man of God, I am very grateful.
What is your advice in the whole world
and the people that are still there,
where you are coming from?
Praise God!
First and foremost, I am grateful to the man of God.
I want to advise everyone here that the
Anointing Water is one stop shop.
Once you get the Anointing Water,
whatsoever is the problem - it's over.
You can imagine, I was the only person
selected from Africa.
Just like that, I knew nobody there.
But as small as I am, the Anointing
Water made me great.
I give God all the praise!
Amen! Thank you, thank you!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 03/01/2019